https://www.richardbrothersfinancial.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Pursuant to applicable federal and/or state privacy regulations Richard Brothers Financial Advisors (referred to as “Richard Brothers”) is a financial institution that has determined to keep confidential nonpublic personal information about each Richard Brothers client.
Nonpublic personal information is defined to mean personally identifiable financial information that is provided by a consumer to a financial institution, results from any transaction with the consumer or any service performed for the consumer, or is otherwise obtained by the financial institution.
Personally identifiable financial information means any information: (1) a consumer provides to a financial institution to obtain a financial product or service; (2) about a consumer resulting from any transaction involving a financial product or service between a financial institution and a consumer; or (3) a financial institution otherwise obtains about a consumer in connection with providing a financial product or service to that consumer.
Attached hereto and made a part hereof is a copy of Richard Brothers’s Privacy Notice that is to be distributed by Richard Brothers: (1) initially: (a) to each existing Richard Brothers client; and (b) to each new client prior to or at the time of establishing a “customer relationship” with Richard Brothers; and (2) annually thereafter for as long as the client maintains its relationship with Richard Brothers.
The purpose of Richard Brothers’s Privacy Notice, Privacy Policy as well as its underlying procedures is to protect the confidentiality and security of its clients’ nonpublic personal information.  The categories of nonpublic personal information that Richard Brothers collects from a client depend upon the scope of the client engagement.  It may include information about the client’s personal finances, information about the client’s health to the extent that it is needed for the planning process, information about transactions between the client and third parties, and information from consumer reporting agencies. Richard Brothers has instituted certain technical, administrative and physical safeguards through which Richard Brothers seeks to protect this nonpublic personal informationabout current and former clients from unauthorized use and access.  First, technical procedures are used in order to limit the accessibility and exposure of client information contained in electronic form. Second, administrative procedures are used in order to control the number and type of employees, affiliated and nonaffiliated persons, to whom customer information is accessible.  Third, physical safeguards have been established to prevent access to client information contained in hard-copy form.  As illustrated above, Richard Brothers realizes the importance of information confidentiality and security, and emphasizes practices which are aimed at achieving those goals.
By visiting Richard Brothers website, completing forms and downloading content, you acknowledge, understand, and accept: (1) your obligation to comply with Richard Brothers’s Privacy Policy as set forth on the attached Privacy Notice; (2) that your knowing or reckless violation of this Privacy Policy will result in discipline by Richard Brothers, including the potential termination of your employment; and (3) that if you have any question(s) regarding any aspect of the Privacy Policy, including exceptions thereto, you shall immediately address such question(s) with Randall J. Richard, Chief Compliance Officer, prior to taking any action that could result in the violation of the Privacy Policy. A complete copy of the applicable federal and/or state privacy regulations is available for your review upon request.
Personal Wealth Management
Portfolio & Asset Management
Corporate Solutions
About Us
My Account
Blog
News
Resources
